{
    "subject": "resource/Norma_Fox_Mazer",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Children's_literature",
    "human_readable": "Norma Fox Mazer writes Children's literature.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9027888178825378,
            "question": "What makes Norma Fox Mazer's Children's literature unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8972695469856262,
            "question": "What type of literature does Norma Fox Mazer write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8285863995552063,
            "question": "Is Norma Fox Mazer known for writing adult fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7519712448120117,
            "question": "Who is the author of Children's literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723264753818512,
            "question": "What themes are often explored in Norma Fox Mazer's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699181854724884,
            "question": "Has Norma Fox Mazer written books for other age groups?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6969712972640991,
            "question": "What are some examples of books written by Norma Fox Mazer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6409810185432434,
            "question": "What genre of books is Norma Fox Mazer associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5653747916221619,
            "question": "What age group does Norma Fox Mazer's writing target?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27016088366508484,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Norma Fox Mazer's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norma Fox Mazer writes Children's literature.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7495_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What age group does Norma Fox Mazer's writing target?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7495_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of books is Norma Fox Mazer associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7495_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of books written by Norma Fox Mazer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7495_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7495_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that according to the documents, Norma Fox Mazer does write children's literature."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Norma Fox Mazer is an author of young adult literature, which falls under the broader category of children\u2019s literature. Thus, the statement \"Norma Fox Mazer writes Children's literature\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context does not specify that Norma Fox Mazer writes Children's literature. Although her books are primarily written for young adults, she has also written books that can be considered as appropriate for readers aged ten and up, which includes an older age group than children.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}